[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "The point is the gun, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, I think that is a big -- a big part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "-- which is do you agree with that Sandy Hook father's premise that the right of his child's life supersedes any rights under the Second Amendment to own a high-powered magazine or an assault rifle?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "VBZ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, I believe life is the most precious right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Kellyanne, I mean, unless I'm mistaken, you share the view that the NRA put out, which is that you don't solve the gun violence problem in America by reducing the number of guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, I just first want to say thank you to Van Jones because I couldn't have said it better myself, and I agree with everything he said.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "The big question to me is, who is actually going to stand up and realize the more guns you have out there, the more gun violence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", ",", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "For me, that is also a no-brainer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "I mean, is that the worst thing that could be said about a country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, it's certainly good to hear that from the Jamaican government.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "I'm fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What can you tell me about those developments?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, we won in the appellate court, a reversal of two of the four misdemeanor convictions, and Miss (INAUDIBLE) and I are preparing, even started today, we will be filing some more pleas in the appellate court seeking further relief to dismiss all of those remaining two charges.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Did Casey see the movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I did watch the movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "And did Casey herself see the movie, do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "You know what, I don't -- I spoke with her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "How are you going to try and work through this in terms of client management and changing public perception?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, I guess there's so many things we have to worry about changing in society.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "How do you change people's mentalities about some things that they're just married to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I mean, one of the ways, of course, could be that she gives an interview, perhaps to me on this show, and speaks honestly for an hour about her experience and tries to communicate with the American public who still doubt her innocence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Obviously, the case, the trial tore them all apart, but has there been any repairing of the damage there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "How is she coping with this on a human level?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "The best way I can describe it is with anxiety.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "And if she does, what is the kind of reaction that she gets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "She does not have current exposure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "You would do anything for your child, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Can you shed any light on this, David?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I think it's all mysterious.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Has she had another wardrobe malfunction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "It's like the ultimate thing that you would wish for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "USSELL: I'm very proud of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Hi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Do you plead guilty to all those descriptions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I'm going to have to read over them again but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Are you rude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Well, unintentionally, yes, unfortunately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Are you dirty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Well, I mean -- I'm not dirty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Are you foul-mouthed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Are you going to try and change that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Yes, I am working on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Are you going to try to be better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Are you sloppy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Are you sexy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "You don't think you're sexy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "What do you think when you look in the mirror?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Well -- I -- I just -- I'm just trying to figure out what to do with what I got.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Vulnerable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "You're the best actress in the world right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "My pants fell off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Your pants fell off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Well, wait, somebody trips me on the way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130131pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Your pants?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]